<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><tenant><company><name>3D QuickTools Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>3dqp_logo.gif</logo><location>Unit 115, 1/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Micky Ng</person><tel>(852) 2788 2832</tel><fax>(852) 2777 6676</fax><url>www.3dquickpress.com</url><email>info@3dquickpress.com</email><profile>3D QuickTools Ltd. 100% focuses on tool and die industry. It started to provide high quality progressive die design solutions in 1994.  The latest product, 3DQuickPress ® , is integrated with SolidWorks ® aiming at ultimate performance; ease of use and short learning curve to enable tooling engineers to use the power of 3D design. It provides solutions ranging from blanking development; strip layout design and die set structure design. 3DQuickPress ® is the key to get the tremendous benefits from 3D modeling.</profile></company><company><name>ASIC Technology Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 602, 6/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Alex Wong</person><tel>(852) 2423-5688</tel><fax>(852) 2423-5707</fax><url>http://www.asiczone.com</url><email>alex@asiczone.com</email><profile>This company develops an ASIC (application specific integrated circuit) which integrates a modem and Internet connection functions so that it can directly dial up and communicate with the Internet Service Provider via public network.</profile></company><company><name>ATPATH Technologies Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 103A, 1/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Esmond Lo</person><tel>(852) 2856-3801</tel><fax>(852) 3007-8939</fax><url>http://www.atpath.com</url><email>esmond1@atpath.com</email><profile>Founded in 1998, ATPATH Technologies is an international technology provider that offers Business Process Management (BPM) solutions to enterprise of all sizes. 
As a leading technology innovator, ATPATH Technologies delivers highly flexible end-to-end BPM solutions to global enterprises in Asia-Pacific, Europe and the US. Our solutions are designed to meet the needs of all major industry sectors including Healthcare/ Pharmaceutical, Fast Moving Consumer Goods, Food and Beverage, Banking and Financial Institutions, Governments Institutions, Telecommunications, and more. 
Fully leveraging the advantage of our global presence, ATPATH Technologies established its R&D and software development site in Guangzhou Science Park, China PRC. Combining the state-of-the-art technology expertise of China team and in-depth project management and customer support capabilities of the global team, ATPATH Technologies has unique competitive advantage. ATPATH Technologies represents a new generation of technology company that can both build on the economics and technical advantages of WTO China, but also combine this with international expertise to create a global presence. 
ATPATH Technologies also provides consulting and systems integration services, technical support and training for customers. Our professional services team, which has a wide range of technical expertise, offers integrated services that ensure your success with our technology. We work closely with you as a team to guarantee that you get the maximum return on investment and ensure your business is running on the right path.</profile></company><company><name>Acasia Technologies (HK) Limited</name><industry>Photonics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 501-506, 5/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2612-8888</tel><fax>(852) 2480-4757</fax><url>http://www.acasiatech.com</url><email>info@acasiatech.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Advanced Analogic Technologies (Hong Kong) Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 608-613, 6/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 8101-1835</tel><fax>(852) 8101-1329</fax><url>http://www.analogictech.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Advanced Packaging Technology Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 205-205A, 2/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Advanced Wireless Group Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 208-211, 2/F, Bio-Informatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin</location><person>Mr. Lai Soon Peng</person><tel>26358111</tel><fax>26327030</fax><url>http://www.aw-g.com</url><email>splai@aw-g.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Advantek Biologics Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>unit 538-539, 5/F,, 1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms Claro Ho</person><tel>852 - 2869 6401</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Agile Software Corporation</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>agile_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 227-230, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607-4030</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4031</fax><url>http://www.agile.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>AirGini Asia Pacific Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>AirGini_Logo_200_64.jpg</logo><location>Unit 213, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607 4308</tel><fax>(852) 2607 4318</fax><url>http://www.airgini.com</url><email>info@airgini.com</email><profile>AirGini is a mobile technology start-up focused on making it easy, useful and enjoyable for people to discover, access and embrace contents that matter to them.</profile></company><company><name>Akos Advanced Technolgoy Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>AkosLogo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 206, Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Ave, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Teresa Law</person><tel>(852) 2947 0332</tel><fax>(852) 2947 0116</fax><url>http://www.akos.com.hk</url><email>teresa@akos.com.hk</email><profile>Akos's mission is to provide high quality and professional services, and products that meet the needs of our clients and customers.  Our multi-disciplinary development groups are guided by directors and senior engineering staff, who are skilled and experienced professionals. To enhance hands-on design approaches and products, we emphasize customer-oriented, problem solving, innovative and professional designs, imagination and creativity.

We provide competent engineering design and supervision in the fields of building services engineering, environmental engineering, energy management, and educational media.

Our products include air purifier, water purifier and intelligent environmental monitoring system. Our services include Advanced Technology Transfer, Consultancy Services on Environmental Impact Assessment, Design and Build for Intelligent Building, Educational Software and Hardware Development, Green Technology and Product Development, Laboratory Testing and Consultancy Services on air, water and material samples.</profile></company><company><name>Altai Technologies Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 103B & 105, 1/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Lin Chi Hung</person><tel>(852) 3580 0223</tel><fax>(852) 3580 0220</fax><url>/</url><email>chlin@altaitechnologies.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Amonics Limited</name><industry>Photonics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 206-208, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Ray Man</person><tel>(852) 2428-9723</tel><fax>(852) 2428-9704</fax><url>http://www.amonics.com</url><email>rayman@amonics.com</email><profile>Amonics is developing the Erbium Doped Fiber Amplifier (EDFA) technology, which works like a pump to boost the strength of optical signals and will enhance the performance of fibre optic communication networks. Base on this technology, Amonics intends to develop a series of product.</profile></company><company><name>AnTech MPS (Global) Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>AnTech_Logo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 218, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Boris S.C. Yip</person><tel>2667 0660</tel><fax>3167 1782</fax><url>http://www.antech.hk</url><email>bscy@antech.hk</email><profile>AnTech MPS (Global) Limited was established with charter to develop, market and maintain the patent licensed product IMPRAMS – which stands for Interface for Mobile Private Remote Access to Media Source.  IMPRAMS product aims to enhance usage of mobile phone wireless network (2G/3G/WiFi) facilities through enabling of communication between mobile handset/PDA and the private computing device at home or in office via the wireless and ground networks connecting the devices together.  Private data or media can be accessed online and directed for display on own handset or on other screen.  By providing more private usages to the handset user will definitely arouse the interest of private media access and hence more frequent access to the wireless phone network.  This is the distinct advantage IMPRAMS product can be envisaged to assist mobile phone network operators to increase the registered subscriber base and hence the corresponding operating ARPU from overall subscription revenue.</profile></company><company><name>Andigilog International Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 707, 7/F, Innovation Centre, 6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Bill Sheppard</person><tel>14809406200</tel><fax>14809402455</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Antonio Precise Products Manufactory Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>LOGO_2.JPG</logo><location>Unit 307-313, 3/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Maggie Chan – HR & Admin. Officer</person><tel>(852) 2952-7695</tel><fax>(852) 2952-7595</fax><url>http://www.antonio.com</url><email>maggie.wt.chan@antonio.com</email><profile>Established in 1982, Antonio Precise Products Manufactory Ltd ("ATO") has been renowned for its design and technology in manufacturing top quality headphones and headsets. Not only has ATO achieved outstanding progress. In the past two decades, we also become one of the key market players in the headphones & headsets industries winning remarkable compliment from clients all over the world. The name "ATO" is self-explanatory to our international success :

A - for the Assurance of total qualtiy and complete customer satisfaction.

T - the Teamwork that builds the crucial partnerships with our customers.

O - for the Originally of our designs and the innovation of our products.

ATO welcome the new millennium with the introduction of the Bluetooth and wireless product series. Cutting-edge technology combines with dynamic design are inspired to provide extra comfort and convenience for daily usage. We even take a bigger stride and extend our product range to Digital Audio MP3. Riding on our expertise in audio equipment. Versatile Mp3 players mixed with various types of headsets and earphones will be inaugurated in 2004.</profile></company><company><name>AppoTech Limited</name><industry>Semiconductor</industry><logo>AnTech_Logo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 110-111, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Chuck Cheng</person><tel>(852) 2607-4090</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4096</fax><url>http://www.appotech.com</url><email>info@appotech.com</email><profile>Founded in Hong Kong, January 2003, AppoTech is a fabless IC design house dedicating in providing high performance, high reliability, high flexibility and cost effective solutions. With headquarters in Hong Kong, branch offices in US, AppoTech aspires to be the leading fabless semiconductor company developing application specific processor-based System-on-Chip (SoC) by offering innovative and cost effective solutions based on advanced technology from Silicon Valley and the efficient cost structure of Asia.
Founded by a group of entrepreneurs in USA, we have gained many years of valuable experience and skill sets in developing microcontrollers and microprocessors. Over the past years, our entrepreneurs have developed Pentium/SPARC class processors, automobile and home appliance microcontrollers etc. They have brought back the world-class MCU design technology and know-how together with the excellent business track record and customer connections to AppoTech.
AppoTech is going to develop a series of products ranging from low-end to high-end with great performance of 10MIPS – 10,000MIPS CPU/DSP targeting for the applications of high-speed data interface, wireless and control, MPEG 4, DSP, logic control and electronic glue etc. Our solutions have a lot of value propositions such as high performance, high flexibility, cost effective, highly integrated, low power consumption, self-developed IPs and high reliability. AX1001 is our first product with great performance of 100 MIPS . With a high speed processor, AX1001 can run 20 times faster than the similar MCU in the market.</profile></company><company><name>Aquent LLC</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 205 & 206, 2/F, Philips Electronics Building, No. 5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Paul Slezak</person><tel>2127 7740</tel><fax>2127 7748</fax><url>http://www.aquent.com</url><email>pslezak@aquent.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>AsiaPac Net Media Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 338, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2771-7595</tel><fax>(852) 2310-2610</fax><url>http://www.asiapac.com.hk</url><email>info@asiapac.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Aspheric Optics</name><industry>Photonics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 216-217, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2793-5976</tel><fax>(852) 2793-1696</fax><url>http://www.aspheric.com</url><email>manfok@aspheric.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Avant Wave Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 315, 3/F, Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Jonathan Lee</person><tel>2952 7188</tel><fax>2646 3713</fax><url>http://www.avantwave.com</url><email>sclee@avantwave.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Aztech Systems (HK) Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>aztech_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 302-310, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Michael Mun</person><tel>(852) 2757-1177</tel><fax>(852) 2757-0578</fax><url>http://www.aztech.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Babi Mobile Media Company Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 208C, 2/ F, No. 5 Science Park West Ave, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Beez Network Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>beezlogo.JPG</logo><location>Unit 209A, 2/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Simon Ho</person><tel>(852 ) 2345 1923</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.beez.com.hk</url><email>info@beez.com.hk</email><profile>Beez professed in launching portals empowered by latest java web technology. Products includes up4food.com, wedding2.com.hk and L3.com.hk. Using J2EE, We developed busysquare.com, a scheduling tool on web used for inviting and reminding you or your clients of events.  Currently, industry using it includes education and trading as a scheduling solution.</profile></company><company><name>Beyjing Design & Creation (HK) Co. Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 512-513, 5/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Emma Ho</person><tel>2854 2731</tel><fax>2391 6796</fax><url>http://www.bdnc.com.hk</url><email>emma@bdnc.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Bio-Cancer Treatment International Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 511 - 513, 5/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Ada Chan</person><tel>(852) 2521 1566</tel><fax>(852) 2521 1560</fax><url>http://www.bio-cancer.org</url><email>wmchan@bio-cancer.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Bloombase Technologies Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>bloombase-logo_least-invasi.jpg</logo><location>Unit 219B, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Jemmee Yung</person><tel>(852)3690-2928</tel><fax>(852)3690-2128</fax><url>http://www.bloombase.com</url><email>jemmee.yung@bloombase.com</email><profile>Bloombase Technologies formulated a vision for the next generation of application-specific enterprise information security equipment to secure computing infrastructure and accelerate e-commerce. This vision brings together cryptography, heterogeneous high-speed network, service-oriented and ASIC technologies to yield least invasive solutions to be able to support the security, simplicity and performance required for wide adoption.

To address the growing enterprise data security issues and achieve maximum data confidentiality, privacy, integrity and source identity, Bloombase Technologies develops and markets Spitfire security solutions. 
Electronic enterprise data are invaluable corporate assets which should never be disclosed to or tampered by unauthorized parties. Statistics have shown that there is a growing trend of data attack at the core which introduces direct financial and goodwill loss to numerous enterprises. Unlike traditional access control and other perimeter security products, Spitfire security solutions can effectively protect enterprise data from attacks at the core.

Spitfire SOA Security Server is a standalone appliance for EAI and EDI data security accelerating real-world e-business. Spitfire StoreSafe is an enterprise class networked storage security appliance for wire-speed storage data encryption. Spitfire Messaging Server secures enterprise messaging systems from phishing vulnerabilities and protects confidential messages from prying eyes.</profile></company><company><name>Blue Solve Limited</name><industry>Electronic Engineering - IC Design</industry><logo>blue_slove.jpg</logo><location>Unit 109, 1/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Louise Au</person><tel>(852) 2607-4018</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4096</fax><url>http://www.bluesolve.com</url><email>Info@bluesolve.com</email><profile>BLUESOLVE is a fabless semiconductor company designing high performance analog/radio frequency integrated circuits for the demanding RF marketplace. The company has successfully developed a series of IC for low power RF communication including VLF Receiver, 27MHz-100MHz FM transmitter, 2.4GHz power amplifier and low noise amplifier for WLAN and wireless audio. The developed solutions and chips were mostly applied in health care product, sports equipment, low power portable device and wireless monitoring system. 

Besides developing proprietary IC, BlueSolve provides ASIC design services from schematic capture, circuit analysis and design, simulation and layout,  IC testing to prototype construction. 
BlueSolve is founded in 2002 and being selected to join the Incubation Program in Hong Kong Science and Technology Park in 2003, to enjoy the most advanced IC design facility in the region. The company then gained Innovation & Technology Fund(ITF) for research and development of an RFIC capturing universal RCC signals in 2004 and 2005. BlueSolve's effort on technological research and the product invention is also acknowledged by HKUST that the company was selected in the HKUST Entrepreneurship program in 2004. 
BlueSolve strives to apply its R & D result such as analog circuit design, process technology and device characterization to enhance the capabilities of low power RF chip. With strong determination and RF expertise, BlueSolve is poised to be a leading company in the micro power analog IC market.</profile></company><company><name>Bona Fide (Holdings) Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 213-215, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Edmond Wong</person><tel>(852) 2655-8199</tel><fax>(852) 2345-2377</fax><url>http://www.bonafide.com.hk</url><email>edmond@bonafide.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Bridgetech Medical Technologies Research & Development Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 503 & 505, 5/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Carrie Yuen</person><tel>(852) 2114 4994</tel><fax>(852) 2110 5780</fax><url>/</url><email>carrie.yuen@bthi.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>C-Link Research & Development Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Leung Yin Ling/ Mr. Tsang Yan Chi</person><tel>(852) 2603 7160</tel><fax>(852) 2603 7160</fax><url>http://www.cnc-authentication.com</url><email>enquiry@cnc-authentication.com</email><profile>Thermoluminescence (TL) dating method applied to ceramics is the only scientific method so far that provides absolute dating, meaning that the time of manufacture can be arrived at independently by TL measurements alone. The technical staff previously worked at the Chinese University of Hong Kong to provide commercial TL service, since January 2001, together with the facilities become part of C&C Authentication Laboratory Limited to meet the new demands of the clients.</profile></company><company><name>CK Information Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 209C, 2/F, No. 5 Science Park West Ave, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 3583 2305</tel><fax>(852) 3589 2304</fax><url>www.ckit.com.hk</url><email>wkkan@ckit.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>CSMC Technologies Corporation</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 510, 5/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Raymond Tong</person><tel>(852) 2668 9369</tel><fax>(852) 2668 9800</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>China Aerospace Telecommunications Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 101, 1/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2627-3388</tel><fax>(852) 2363-7973</fax><url>http://www.castelecom.com</url><email>castel@castelecom.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>China Electronic Information Technology Ltd</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 715-716, 7/F, No. 6 Science Park West Avenue, IC development Centre, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, NT</location><person>Dr. Richard Wong</person><tel>2575-6111</tel><fax>2192-1818</fax><url>http://www.ceithk.com</url><email>richard@ceithk.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Chinese American Semiconductor Professional Association</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 116C, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Chip and System Technology Centre</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 701, 7/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2836-1793</tel><fax>(852) 2832-9443</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Chung Wah Electronics Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit  116, 1/F, Innovation Centre, 6 West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park Pak Shek Kok N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Citi-Wit Energy-Saving Systems Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 301, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2690-2489</tel><fax>(852) 2690-3949</fax><url>http://www.citi-wit.com</url><email>info@citi-wit.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Cluster Technology Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 106-108, 1/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2655-6100</tel><fax>(852) 2994-2101</fax><url>http://www.clustertech.com/</url><email>enquiry@clustertech.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Colisa Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 107A, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Comprehensive Drug Enterprises Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>comprehensive.jpg</logo><location>Unit 210C, 2/F, Photonics Centre,, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Benjamin T Lee</person><tel>(852) 2607-4100</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4150</fax><url>www.cdelimited.com</url><email>blee@cdelimited.com</email><profile>Comprehensive Drug Enterprises Limited (CDE) is engaged in the research, development, and commercialization of sublingually and nasally administered forms of pharmaceuticals.  The sublingual and nasal delivery of certain pharmaceuticals may enable more rapid systemic absorption, lower required dosages, quicker onset of desired effect, and painless, convenient patient self-administration, resulting in improved patient compliance and pharmacoeconomics.  The company focuses its research primarily on drugs with demonstrated safety and efficacy, which through their current delivery forms have certain bioavailability, or therapeutic limitations that may be improved with sublingual or nasally delivery system.  By optimizing CDE’s transmucosal drug delivery platform, our technology will reveal the full potential of sublingual and intranasal medication.   Our technology platform differentiates existing pharmaceutical products, making new indications possible and provides proprietary protection, thereby reducing competition from manufacturers of generic drugs.  We believe that large pharmaceutical companies will increasingly seek to establish collaborative agreements with drug delivery specialist like CDE.</profile></company><company><name>Computer Applications Co. Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 103 & 105, 1/F, Philips Electronics Building,, No.5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Dickson Wong</person><tel>(852) 2319 2282</tel><fax>(852) 2319 2943</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ConvenientPower HK Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 207, 2/F,, No. 6 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Cornice Holdings International Inc.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 320, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. KF Cheng</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Cotco Holdings Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 611-620, 6/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2424-8228</tel><fax>(852) 2422-2373</fax><url>http://www.cotco.com</url><email>devsales@cotco.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Credence (HKSP) Customer Support Office</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G06, G/F & 208A, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Cree Asia-Pacific Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 309-310 & 321, 3/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.cree.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Cypress Semiconductor International (HK) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 706-707, 7/F,, Bio- Informatics Centre (Building 6),, No. 2 Science Park West Avenue, HKSP,, Shatin, N. T. Hong Kong</location><person>Ms. Ivy Leung</person><tel>2420 2568</tel><fax>2427 0335</fax><url>www.http://cypress.com</url><email>pcutmp1@cypress.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>DIYSite.com Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 109, 1/F, Philips Electronics Building,, No.5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Polly Lo</person><tel>(852) 2626 0909</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Dao Lab Limited</name><industry>Telecom</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 207B, 2/F, Building 9, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Christine Tong</person><tel>2607 4377</tel><fax>2607 4260</fax><url>http;//www.dao-lab.com</url><email>Christine.tong@dao-lab.com</email><profile>Dao Laboratory develops advanced interactive audio and video technology optimized for the mobility and multi-purpose networks. The company is found and totally owned by Eno Tsin. The entire team is totally based in Hong Kong with the R&D and intellectual property all created and owned by the company. The company comprises 5 permanent staffs responsible for management, business development, sales, engineering and support functions. As the team of Dao Laboratory comprises mostly industrial veterans and our products are already making sales locally and regionally, we have already signed up with two large regional system integrators and resellers to support and distribute our products.
Dao Laboratory has a small and highly focused R&D that results in a focused and highly competitive product range. The core technology driving all our products are real time multimedia interactive technology. This comprises the delivery of video and audio which also allows interaction of users in real time. Our XTream server brings the first truly real time adaptive video delivery that deliver consistent video and audio quality over networks fluctuating bandwidth.  Our GammaVision re-invent the human based audio and video interaction by transforming the highly successful IVR system into full multimedia interaction with video, computer input voice and more. 
Dao Laboratory’s product portfolio covers mobile network operators, content providers, marketing companies and enterprises. XTream Network edition is now under trial with major local and regional mobile network for 3G and 3.5G real time video and audio delivery. GammaVision is destined to be the 3G version of the IVR system which we are establishing trial site and re-seller regionally. 

Dao Laboratory’s major product is GammaVision. GammaVision is a multi-mode  interactive video system that can run on a 3G network. It enables human to human video interaction and human to machine data interaction to perform at the same time on a 3G video phone. As an example of this, consider an online banking service and a phone banking service. When you use a phone banking service you are served by a human who provides you with the flexibility of relatively non-restrictive dialogue. But when you need to enter account number, amount, password and other related figural information, you would find online banking more effective. GammaVision is not an online banking solution nor is it designed for any particular industry or service segment, GammaVision provides the technology that allow any industrial and services segment to leverage the power of a combined interactive modes into a multi-mode interaction. So with GammaVision, for example, on a 3G mobile phone you can dial a number to make a video call to a customer service officer, seeing her face as you speak to her directly, and whenever it comes to the need of entering information, she can present you with a computer like input alert so that you an simply key-in the required information, and when you are not even sure whether you need to hit that enter key at the end, you can always ask the customer service officer right on the screen. That is the power of multi-mode interaction of GammaVision. 

Hyper-Compression
Nearly all video that are made for streaming are made with the assumption that it is to be viewed through the Internet and PC. These videos are encoded in a format that works effectively when sufficient network bandwidth is available, this usually means ADSL network of 1.5Mbps or above. Video made to stream over the Internet or LAN is encoded to use 5 to 10 times the bandwidth available on the 3G mobile network, and 10-30 times the bandwidth available on 2.5G network. 
The conventional way of compressing video is part of the Video Encoding Processing. To compress a video to smaller bandwidth requirement (Bit-rate) it involves the combination of techniques such as reducing the Frame-rate and resolution. Unfortunately these conventional techniques doesn’t work well. Reducing Frame-rate means action will be very jerky (that’s why most mobile video shows you news reporter with no action), reducing resolution makes text looks bad. Worst of all, even by combining both techniques the result is just barely enough to fit into a good 3G bandwidth, with 2.75G or 2.5G totally out of question. 
Dao Lab’s hyper compression technique can work with any type of video encoding, it achieve a 20 to 40% extra size reduction on top of any existing encoding format from standard MPEG4 to H.264 high definition video. It make use of the fact that the small screen size (and resolution) of the mobile devices provides an unique opportunity to leverage traditional de-noising technique which generate a substantial reduction on the result video size. By applying this to dedicated hardware codec, we can successfully accelerate to the level that real time hyper-compression is possible. With hyper-compression, we can deliver video to even 2.5G handset at a frame-rate of higher than today’s standard 3G video streaming rate.
Clear Start 
Our statistics and real world experience both confirms that as many as over 50% of mobile video streaming fails because of a failed start. The common problem is exhibit in the form of a “green screen” or “ghost screen” that may either go away after a while or may cause the mobile video player to malfunction. 
We have created a unique proprietary technology that can totally eliminate such “green / ghost screen” problem to ensure a successful and proper start of video playback. This technology is designed to work with even the existing video players without modification. It’s a technology we shall patent and therefore we cannot disclose the detail design at this moment.
Server Side Adaptive Delivery
Apart from the fail-to-start problem, another commonly encountered problem on video delivery over all kind of channels, including mobile and the Internet / LAN, is that of a fluctuating bandwidth. For wireless network, fluctuation is caused by the change of radio signal strength (partly due to interference, partly due to deflection), for cable networks, that is mostly due to packetization allocation of traffic and the lack of QoS. Using conventional technique, a video is encoded to a certain size (bit-rate), better quality means larger size and vice versa. However, when bandwidth drops, a video of good quality under high bandwidth will become a video of very poor quality under low bandwidth. In a mobile environment, a viewer can move from a location with good signal reception to an area with poor signal in a relatively short period of time, as a result, more than often a video may fail to play before the viewing completes.
One key part of our technology is to tackle this fluctuation of bandwidth problem. Our server side based technology involves two parts: One is a technology to detect the available effective bandwidth, the other is a technology that allows the server to continuously change the bit rate of the delivered video whenever it detects a change of bandwidth.</profile></company><company><name>Diffractive Optics Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 216-217, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Roger Leung</person><tel>2793 5976</tel><fax>2793 1696</fax><url>http://www.aspheric.com</url><email>roger@aspheric.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Doro Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 222, 2/F, Building 2, N0.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T</location><person>Mr. Andrew Leung</person><tel>2730 2777</tel><fax>2730 2433</fax><url>http://www.doro.com.hk</url><email>andrew.leung@doro.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>DragonTech Corporation Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>dragontech.jpg</logo><location>Unit 219A, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Edwin Lui</person><tel>2607 4013</tel><fax>2607 4043</fax><url>http://www.dragontechcorp.com</url><email>info@dragontechcorp.com</email><profile>Established in 2005 and founded by a group of IT veterans, Dragontech Corporation Limited is a network product developer committed to developing practical network products and various IT solutions particularly for small and medium-sized businesses.

Product
ioBox™, a truly all-in-one network appliance, gives you the ability to employ advanced network technologies at a low cost. The all-in-one design combines different network and server features, from traffic shaping router, 8-port switch, stateful firewall, WiFi access point, web server, email server, webmail server, ftp server, file server, database server, VPN server to DHCP server and RAS server into one box while its small in size is perfect for SME premises.  The GUI Management Engine facilitates instant service deployment via a highly integrated web interface.  Its Instant-Domain-Name™ feature allows SMEs to setup their own unique domain names in seconds.  Together with the RAID data protection and redundant cooling fans, reliability is greatly enhanced and brings the business user peace of mind.

One box to setup and support, ioBox™ provides secure and robust total network solution, and the all-in-one design minimizes the total cost of ownership.  The product is an innovative, practical and hassle-free device for employing advanced network technologies at an affordable cost.</profile></company><company><name>Dragonchip Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 303-305, 3/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Felix Wong</person><tel>(852) 2776-0111</tel><fax>(852) 2776-0996</fax><url>http://www.dragonchip.com</url><email>felix.wong@dragonchip.com</email><profile>This company designs, manufactures and markets
Embedded Flash Micro Controller Unit (MCU).</profile></company><company><name>DynaCity Technology (HK) Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>Logo_DynaCity_jpg1.jpg</logo><location>Unit 108, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Miss Cherry Poon</person><tel>(852) 2265-8160</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2582</fax><url>http://www.dynacitytech.com</url><email>dctcherry@dynacitytech.com</email><profile>DynaCity Technology (HK) Limited was established in 2003, located in Hong Kong Science Park. The company carries out developing, manufacturing and marketing of a range of advanced motion controller/driver products, and CNC machine devices. The company also performs ASIC design and provides various consulting and supporting services. 

As one of the few regional companies focusing on continuous innovation of high-tech motion control/driving solutions, DynaCity’s products employ the state-of-the-art technology. The founders of the company have rich experience in both technology and business aspects. A group of experts in high-tech and management are leading DynaCity to offer its clients highly customized total system solution to address the specific application needs.

DynaCity obtained 2003 Hong Kong Award for Industry. The product development has received the Innovation Technology Funds.</profile></company><company><name>E-Mice Solutions (HK) Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>emice_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 523, 525-530, 5/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Eva Chan</person><tel>(852) 2511-9393</tel><fax>(852) 2511-6969</fax><url>http://www.e-mice.net</url><email>support@e-mice.net</email><profile>E-MICE Solutions Limited is principally involved in the information technology and telecommunications industries.  The company is a leading CRM solution provider to telecom operators in Asia, with solutions including Operational CRM and Analytical CRM.  The immediate goal is to be the leading provider of e-CRM systems for selective, vertical markets.  Our long-term vision is to be our clients’ partner in e-CRM systems development as they evolve from being in-house departments to e-CRM hosting entities for their industries. 

The Company’s customers include some of the largest telecom operators in the Greater China Region.  As competition within the telecom industry intensifies, these telecom service providers require state-of-the-art, highly integrated, real time sales and marketing and customer management systems, which can substantially improve their competitive position in their respective markets.  As a result, E-MICE will devote considerable efforts in continuously upgrading its Operational and Analytical CRM solutions in coming years in meeting its customers’ needs.

E-mice Technologies Group Limited
Related companies:-

E-mice Holdings Limited
E-mice Networks Limited, E-mice Networks (HK) Limited
E-mice solutions Limited, E-mice Solutions (HK) Limited</profile></company><company><name>EDA Centre & Data Centre</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park Avenue West, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Peter Yeung</person><tel>2784 2667</tel><fax>2788 4261</fax><url>http://www.hkstp.org</url><email>peter.yeung@hkstp.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>EDS</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>/</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>EM Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 507, 5/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2195 3828</tel><fax>(852) 2741 1481</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>EMSD</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>/</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Electro-Thermal-Technologies & Components Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 212, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Christine Zheng</person><tel>(852) 2144-2662</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2663</fax><url>http://www.electrovac.com</url><email>zhe@electrovac.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Entropic Communication (HK) Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 313, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue &, Unit 315, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Fred Leung</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.entropic.com</url><email>fleung@entropic.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Everplant Technology Limited</name><industry>Biotechnology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 211, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Jeffery Kan</person><tel>(852) 2482-2961</tel><fax>(852) 2482-7185</fax><url>http://www.everplant.com</url><email>cykan@everplant.com</email><profile>Everplant Technology Ltd. is a Hong Kong based company founded by a group of highly experienced entrepreneurs and scientists specializing in development of preserved plants. By applying our cutting-edge biotechnology and superior preserve process to real plants, we supply the preserved plants of various kind and size to different industry sectors in local and international markets. We strive to develop more species of preserved plants with better features and benefits for different customers' needs.(</profile></company><company><name>FiiTech Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>1185272142719_fiitechlogowithname.jpg</logo><location>Unit 209B, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. H. L. Yiu</person><tel>(852) 8122-9608</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.fiitech.com</url><email>hlyiu@fiitech.com</email><profile>FiiTech stands for Fast Idea Integration Solutions and SoC Technology.

Founded by Mr. H.L. Yiu and Mr. Andrew Chu in 2005. Mr. Yiu and Mr. Chu were the founders of the DragonBall family of processors for Palm PDA products in Motorola Semiconductors.

FiiTech provides ODM/OEM customers innovative solutions (software + silicon) for wireless consumer networking markets.</profile></company><company><name>Fuji Electric Device Technology Hong Kong Co. Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 227-231, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Esty Lau</person><tel>3518 3010</tel><fax>2664 8040</fax><url>http://www.fujielectric.com</url><email>esty@hkfd.fujielectric.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Fujitsu PC Asia Pacific Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 603-607, 6/F, No. 2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Cathy Choi</person><tel>3107 8312</tel><fax>3107 8311</fax><url>http://www.fujitsu-pcap.com.hk</url><email>cathy.choi@fujitsu-pcap.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>GP Electronics (HK) Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201-207, 2/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Irene Loi</person><tel>(852) 2410-7794</tel><fax>(852) 2410-7796</fax><url>http://www.gpe-hkg.com</url><email>irene.loi@gpe-hkg.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>GeneHarbor (Hong Kong) Technologies Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 506-507, 5/F, Bio-Informatics Centre, No. 2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Aubrey Cheng</person><tel>2994-3330</tel><fax>2994-3966</fax><url>http://www.geneharbor.com.hk</url><email>aubreycheng@geneharbor.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Go Wireless Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210D, 2/F, Photonics Centre,, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Michael Sivan</person><tel>(852) 3793 3988</tel><fax>(852) 3620 3988</fax><url>http://www.gowireless.com.hk</url><email>msivan@gowireless.com.hk</email><profile>GO Wireless conceptualizes, develops, manufactures and distributes innovative wireless Consumer Electronic, as well as innovative wireless Electronics Toys.

GO WIRELESS focuses on –
-	Innovative – new product ideas, new patent-pending inventions, new concepts
-	Latest wireless technology – latest chipsets, latest reference designs, latest developments
-	Affordable prices – all GO WIRELESS products are carefully defined in advance to meet target unit cost at mass production. Such to provide the required margins of the marketing chain in the Consumer Electronics market, as well as in the Toy market.

GO Wireless manufactures its products mainly at its OEM/ODM factory associates in Bao’an (nearby Shenzhen).

GO WIRELESS target markets are the USE, EU and Japan. GO WIRELESS inherited more than 14 years of business experience in these markets.

GO WIRELESS products are marketed under GO WIRELESS’s own brand “GM”, as well as under private labels of its larger customers.

GO WIRELESS has gained recognition from Hong Kong Government’s Innovation & Technology Commission with a SERAP approved project for one of its latest developments.</profile></company><company><name>Golden Regent Electronics Industries Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 325-326, 3/F, No. 1Science Park West Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>Ms. Rosana Lee</person><tel>2423 3332</tel><fax>2423 3626</fax><url>www.http://goldenregent.com</url><email>rosanalee@goldenregent.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Group Sense Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>6/F & 7/F Unit (708-713, 727-728), No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms.May Chan</person><tel>2832-8218</tel><fax>2631-2810</fax><url>http://www.gsl.com.hk</url><email>samsontam@gsl.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HIS Technologies Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210E, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. William Yuen</person><tel>(852) 3165 8507</tel><fax>(852) 2881 6171</fax><url>http://www.histechs.com</url><email>william@histechs.com</email><profile>HIS Technologies Ltd is a research & development based technology company developing next generation Fiber-based Solutions.  Our system provides multi-service platform for Education Institutions, Corporations, Government, property developers, ISPs, ICPs to deploy concurrent bandwidth demanding services and applications like multiple High Definition Video based program broadcast, live-broadcast, video-on-demand, surveillance system, video conferencing, etc. over a distance of over 50 kilometres.

Our products include a series of inter-connected devices and systems that provide seamless connection with multi-services all the way to the end users (home, desk, classroom, etc.) via single thread of fiber, thereby enabling each user in a location to enjoy, concurrently, over a hundred HDTV channels and other bandwidth-hungry services.</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - BDTS Business Incubation Support Office & Incu-Tech Centre</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6700</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4260</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - BDTS Technology Support Office</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 301-302, 3/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6600</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - Corporate Communications Office / Industry & University Collaboration Office</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 306-307, 3/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607-4040</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - Probe and Test Development Centre</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G01A, G/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6699</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - Product Analysis Laboratory</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 01, G/F Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6683</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - Reliability Lab</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G02, G/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6600</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp.  - Small Enterprise Centre - Science Park Office</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 101-103, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue & Unit 209, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Matherine Lee</person><tel>(852) 2629-6666</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>http://www.hkstp.org</url><email>matherine.lee@hkstp.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HK Sci. & Tech. Parks Corp. - BDTS</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>G/F., Bio-informatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HKITPA</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Room E, Unit 116, 1/F, No. 6 Science Park West Ave, Innovation Centre, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HKSTP Incu-Tech Centre - Science Park Office</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 209, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 - 2607 4110</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HKSTP-BDTS Division (Wireless Laboratory)</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>G/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Peter Yeung</person><tel>(852) 2629 6688</tel><fax>(852) 8607 4070</fax><url>/</url><email>peter.yeung@hkstp.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HKSTPC Corporate Communications Office / HKSTPC Industry & University Collaboration Office</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 306-307, 3/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 - 2607 4040</tel><fax>852 - 2607 4069</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HKiA</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Room F, Unit 116, 1/F, No. 6 Science Park West Ave, Innovation Centre, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HSDL Technologies Limited</name><industry>Electronics/Video/HDTV</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 202A, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Ben Tsoi</person><tel>(852) 2144-2020</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2080</fax><url>http://www.hsdl.hk</url><email>bentsoi@hsdl.hk</email><profile>Development of Mass Storage Intellectual Property Cores 
Technology 
Happy Success¡¦ expertise is in mass storage, including host controllers, device controllers, error correcting codes (ECC) and RAID. Our design team started the first Serial ATA project in the industry and created Serial ATA products that dominate the market. Our team also designed ECC blocks that have been incorporated in hundreds of millions of products. 
Serial ATA is based on, and improved from, parallel ATA. While parallel ATA is an industry standard, there are many deviations from the specification. Serial ATA inherits these deviations. Our knowledge on the subject enables us to support these deviations so that our designs are compatible with most devices and hosts. 
On RAID, our team¡¦s focus is to maximise bandwidth utilisation. Upon a disk failure, the disk must be replaced and rebuilt quickly so that the system can recover before a catastrophic second disk failure. Certain bandwidth of the storage system will be used for the rebuild process. Our architecture allows multiple disk failures. The urgency to rebuild is little and the bandwidth for rebuilding can be greatly reduced. 
Product 

Happy Success¡¦ initial products include an AHCI Serial ATA core and a set of RAID cores. The AHCI Serial ATA core is compliant with ACHI Revision 1.1 and can also support legacy ATA task file accesses. It includes the AHCI and Serial ATA Link and Transport functions. The RAID cores support multiple disk failures in hardware.</profile></company><company><name>Hamster Force Multimedia Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 202, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Chiu Man Chung</person><tel>(852) 9718-3826</tel><fax>(852) 3542-5930</fax><url>http://www.hamsterforce.com</url><email>info@hamsterforce.com</email><profile>Hamster Force Multimedia Limited is a company devoted to interactive products, specifically educational software. We emphasize on not only curricular syllabus, but also extracturricular activities to nurture all-round children. We endeavor to create content by making use of comprehensive information and appealing graphics. It enables child to learn while playing, preferably providing chances to learn and play with their parents. Creative Series is our first product line launched in the market. The characteristics of our Creative Series is to enhance children' imagination and creativity. "Animal Melody", our first product, with main theme on music, it is divided into two prime components. Six intensive tutorials are arranged to teach children fundamental musical theories. Secondly, musical composition facilities are supplied via staff or piano. Here we stimulate midiformat-like sequence output, children can compose, record and play their songs, save as file to share with their families. Emphasis on both academic and creative content, more titles with innovative ideas and 3D graphics will be coming soon as well.</profile></company><company><name>Happiness Cuisine</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2827-8803</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>HealthBaby Biotech (Hong Kong) Co.Ltd</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 103,105 and 106, &116, 1/F, No. 2 Science Park West Avenue, Bio-Informatics Centre, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T</location><person>Mr. Kenneth Huang</person><tel>3529 2396</tel><fax>3529 2396</fax><url>/</url><email>kennethw@healthbanks.com.tw</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hipro Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G07, G/F & Unit 301-307, 317-320 & 322, 3/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Szeto</person><tel>2191-8133</tel><fax>2191-8233</fax><url>http://www.hipro.com.hk</url><email>fl_szeto@hipro.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong & Mainland Software Industry Cooperation Association (HKSICA)</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Room D, Unit 116, 1/F, IC development Centre, No. 6 Science Park West Ave, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Applied Science and Technology Research Institute Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 101-120, 1/F & 507-520, 5/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue &, Unit 301-315, Bio-Informatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 3406-2800</tel><fax>(852) 3406-2801</fax><url>http://www.astri.org</url><email>corporate@astri.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Applied Science and Technology Research Institute Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G01B, G/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Road, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 - 3406 2800</tel><fax>/</fax><url>www.astri.org</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Information Technology Professionals Association Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 116, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Integrated Circuit (IC) Development Suport Centre</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>G/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Jockey Club Institute of Chinese Medicine Ltd.</name><industry>Biotechnology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 703, 7/F, BioInformatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 3551-7300</tel><fax>(852) 3551-7333</fax><url>http://www.hkjcicm.org</url><email>sfhui@hkjcicm.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Microelectronics Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/1114595044650/2.gif</logo><location>Unit 205, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Song Hong Vong</person><tel>(852) 3421-0420</tel><fax>(852) 2384-8456</fax><url>http://www.hkmicro.com</url><email>songvong@hkmicro.com</email><profile>Hong Kong Microelectronics is an analog IC design company. It has a team of creative and experienced designers. We not only provide high performance power management IC but also provide power system solutions. Our product strategy is focused on Application Specific Standard Products and tailor-made IC design services. More information about the company is available online at www.hkmicro.com.</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong RFID Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>HKRFID.jpg</logo><location>Unit 207A, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mike Fung</person><tel>(852) 2165-4708</tel><fax>(852) 3007-1901</fax><url>http://www.hk-rfid.com</url><email>mike@hk-rfid.com</email><profile>Hong Kong RFID Limited is a Hong Kong based consultancy firm specialized in providing innovative RFID solutions to different organizations in Greater China Region. Our total RFID solution combines both HF and UHF RFID technology according to different criteria in different business applications. We provide not only creative ideas to improve the operational efficiency of our clients, but also standard RFID solutions as a more economic-efficient option.

We are working closely with RFID-equipment manufacturers and suppliers in the North America and the Greater China Region. We provide RFID equipments, tags as well as technical support to clients, partners and local system integrators. Hong Kong RFID Limited always welcomes any new partner to collaborate in any RFID project or product promotion. Please contact our representative for more information.</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation (Head Office)</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>8/F, BioInformatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-1818</tel><fax>(852) 2629-1833</fax><url>http://www.hkstp.org</url><email>enquiry@hkstp.org</email><profile>Hong Kong has always been able to build on its economic strengths and develop its own niches in business. The Hong Kong Science and Technology Parks Corporation is established with a world-class infrastructure and support services to provide the; start-to-end-function" facilities for product R&D, Incubation and Production activities all under one organisation. We hope this new initiative will further enhance Hong Kong's unique capacities. 

I warmly welcome you to visit our web-site, and to find out for yourself the exciting business environment and opportunities HKSTP can offer you. Enjoy the tour! 


Victor Lo, GBS, JP 
Chairman 
Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation (Office)</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>G/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-2481</tel><fax>(852) 2629-1833</fax><url>http://www.hkstp.org</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>Hong Kong has always been able to build on its economic strengths and develop its own niches in business. The Hong Kong Science and Technology Parks Corporation is established with a world-class infrastructure and support services to provide the; start-to-end-function" facilities for product R&D, Incubation and Production activities all under one organisation. We hope this new initiative will further enhance Hong Kong's unique capacities. 

I warmly welcome you to visit our web-site, and to find out for yourself the exciting business environment and opportunities HKSTP can offer you. Enjoy the tour! 


Victor Lo, GBS, JP 
Chairman 
Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation - Incu-Tech Centre - Science Park Office</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 209, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 - 2607 4110</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Hong Kong Science & Technology Parks Corporation Product Analysis Laboratory</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 01, G/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 - 2629 6683</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Honoh Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 307, 3/F, 1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Parl Shek Kok, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>I C Development Support Office</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G03, G/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>IC Product Analysis Laboratory / Material Analysis Laboratory / Photonics Development Support Office</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 204-205, 2/F, Photonic Center, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>IQstor Asia Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 217, 2/F, No. 1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Yoanne Hui</person><tel>2155 6488</tel><fax>2155 9488</fax><url>http://www.iqstor.com</url><email>yoanne.hui@ap.iqstor.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ITC Testing</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>/</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Incubation Centre</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 215-222, 2/F, 1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Informatic</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>unit 318, 3/F,, 1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Felix Yung</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Inspire Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210B, 2/F, IC Development Centre,, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Kenny Lee</person><tel>(852) 2607 4241</tel><fax>(852) 2607 4240</fax><url>http://www.inspire-ltd.com</url><email>Kenny.lee@inspire-ltd.com</email><profile>Design, Development, Production and Engineering for Electronic Toys, Games and Learning.</profile></company><company><name>Integrated Circuits Design Centre & Intellectual Property Servicing Centre</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 308, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Integrated Solutions Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>isl.jpg</logo><location>Unit 706-707, 7/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Hilton Law</person><tel>(852) 2263 6111</tel><fax>(852) 2319 2501</fax><url>/</url><email>hiltonl@isl.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>IntelliTech Technologies Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 203A , 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Y.K. Lo</person><tel>(852) 2144-2020</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2080</fax><url>http://www.intellitech.com.hk</url><email>yk_lo@intellitech.com.hk</email><profile>Intellitech is a fabless IC design company which will mainly design MPEG4 decoder chips for the portable/handheld device market.  The design methodology involved is mainly SOC (System-On-Chip). It will integrate the latest DSP core with advanced memory technologies in SOC design methodology to produce IC product solutions for communications (mobile phones), consumer electronics (MP3) and computing markets (PDA. Pocket PC).</profile></company><company><name>JC Optronics Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210B, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Peter Chan</person><tel>(852) 3421 0038</tel><fax>(852) 3421 0087</fax><url>http://www.jcoptronics.com</url><email>peter@jcoptronics.com</email><profile>JC Optronics is a leading developer, marketer and solution provider of high quality fiber Bragg grating products. JC Optronics is founded by a group of FBG scientists and experts who have many years of experience in the FBG technology development, manufacturing as well as on FBG telecom and sensing engineering application. We are committed to provide state-of-the-art fiber optics sensing technology solutions. We understand that future of our business depends on delivering technology advancements to our customers. Whatever it takes, we will work closely with you to see your technology goals and requirements realized.
Honesty, integrity and high standard of professional ethics are the cornerstones of our philosophy.</profile></company><company><name>JV Photonics Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210B, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Leo Ng</person><tel>(852) 2607 4232</tel><fax>(852) 2607 4239</fax><url>http://www.jvphotonics.com</url><email>leong@jvphotonics.com</email><profile>The company specialises in design and develop high power fiber laser systems suitable for a variety of industrial applications.  The propriety technology utilises a free-space/guided-wave hybrid approach, enabling compact and potentially low-cost high-power laser systems to be constructed.</profile></company><company><name>Jade Semiconductor Limited</name><industry>Semiconductor</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 206, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Sicence Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Jones Lang LaSalle Facility Management Services Ltd.</name><industry>Facility Management</industry><logo>/1115273240590/a.GIF</logo><location>G/F,, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Front Desk Officer</person><tel>(852) 2639-8000</tel><fax>(852) 2655-8668</fax><url>http://www.hksciencepark.org</url><email>helpdesk@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>KBK Hong  Kong Co. Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 705-707, 7/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Cozy H. Nakamura / Mr. David Leung</person><tel>(852) 2535-6319</tel><fax>(852) 2535 8639</fax><url>http://www.kbk.net</url><email>cozy@kbk.net; david@kbk.net</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Kontel Data  System Limited</name><industry>IC System Design</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 209, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Li  Wang Hing</person><tel>(852) 2607 4155</tel><fax>(852) 2117 9608</fax><url>http://www.kontel-data.com</url><email>hk@kontel-data.com</email><profile>- Wireless Data System
- Sensor Analog /Digital integrated Circuit
- Active RFID and Measurement Systems</profile></company><company><name>Kopin (HK) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 211, 2/F, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue, Photonic Centre, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin</location><person>Mr. Kenny Chow</person><tel>6071 6766</tel><fax>3007 8987</fax><url>http://www.kopin.com</url><email>kchow@kopin.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>LPI Precision Optics Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G02, G/F, Photonics Centre,, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park ,, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>/</person><tel>2655 8022</tel><fax>2144 2566</fax><url>www.http://Ipipo.com</url><email>btse@Ipipo.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>LRC (International) Company Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 603, 6/F, No. 6 Science Park West Avenus,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Pak Shek Kok,, Sha Tin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>LTK Industries Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>1185268957375_1LogoofLTKIndustriesLtd.jpg</logo><location>Unit 601-610, 6/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Thomas Chaung</person><tel>(852) 2425-4399</tel><fax>(852) 2418-1627</fax><url>http://www.ltkcable.com</url><email>sales@ltkcable.com</email><profile>LTK Industries Limited was established in 1981 and has become one of the most competitive cable-manufacturing enterprises in Asia. With a headquarters in Hong Kong, LTK has operations in Huizhou, Shanghai and Dalian , and sales offices in the USA, Japan, Singapore, China and Taiwan, etc. 

LTK specializes in manufacturing, sales and marketing of high quality wires and cables. Our productsinclude hook-up wires, networking cables, coaxial cables, telecommunication cables, game cables, audio/video cables, high speed interface cables (USB, IEEE1284, IEEE1394, RGB, LCD flat panel, etc), optical fiber cable, building wires and power cords.

Being an honorable manufacturer, LTK is committed to providing high quality service to customers, as well as quality enhancement and diversification of products. . At present, all our high-end manufacturing facilities have attained ISO9000 quality accreditation of BASEC, of which a number of our production facilities have attained ISO14001 quality as well. . Meanwhile, our products have also met the standards set up by BASEC, UL, CSA VDE, KEMA, F-MARK, SAA, CCEE, etc. In addition,  LTK isare proud to be the first UL-certified Cat 5 LAN cable maker who also conforms to TIA/EIA-568-B.2-1 and ISO/IEC 11801 standard in Asia.

LTK’s quality products always meet the rigorous standards set up by different international institutions, in addition to supplying the local area, most of the products are exported to overseas such as Europe, USA, Japan, Taiwan, etc. Our customers include China Telecom, Netcom, Sharp, Hitachi, Mitsubishi, Sony, Hewlett Packard, Motorola, etc. Besides, many prominent OEM  throughout Asia, North America and Europe are current customers of our LTK’s LAN cable, which  are also widely used several government projects such as Finance Bureau, astronomy division, Dalian Telecommunications Bureau, Port Dalian, etc  in China. 

LTK faithfully adheres to the slogan: ‘Dedicated Teamwork Commit Defect Free Performance’ and makes every endeavor to become a recognized leader in the industry.</profile></company><company><name>Label Technology and Automation Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/1132827307975/PrintApplyLogo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 212, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Richard Chan</person><tel>(852) 3576-3132</tel><fax>(852) 2340-7561</fax><url>http://www.printapply.com</url><email>richard@printapply.com</email><profile>Label Technology And Automation Limited (P&A) is an engineering solution provider to help our clients develop robust solutions in label automation such as mechatronic labeling system, label software and RFID middleware fully compliant with EPCglobal standard. 

P&A is sophisticated at developing a series of products suit for use in the packaging business. This accelerates process flow automation in any fast expanding manufacturing industry such as pharmacy, chain stores and facilitates efficiency-demanded supply chain environment, using enabled and the latest technologies.

As a professional engineering service provider, we are fully committed to delivering high quality and practical product solutions. In achieving our commitment, we are adopting leading CAD models in product design, digital simulation and optimization, as well as process flow scenario analysis. This can also accelerate close cooperation among users, designers and fabricators. To help visualize the enhanced supply chain workflow before full investment is made, we provide our clients with digital animation in 3D environment.

Our performance pledge is to provide our clients with the top quality products, high reliability and the best after-sale service, at a competitive price.</profile></company><company><name>Lee's Pharmaceutical (HK) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 110 & 111, 1/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Susanne Luen</person><tel>(852) 2314 1182</tel><fax>(852)2314 1708</fax><url>http://www.leespharm.com</url><email>susanne@leespharm.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Lexiwave Technology (Hong Kong) Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>Lexiwave_logo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 205, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Henry Lau</person><tel>(852) 2144-2592</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2595</fax><url>http://www.lexiwave.com</url><email>info@lexiwave.com</email><profile>Lexiwave Technology (Hong Kong) Ltd. is a design house specializing on Radio Frequency (RF) system and Integrated Circuit (IC) design for communication and consumer products. Members of the management teams have been engaging in design, production and marketing of RF communication products and ICs for more than 45 man-years worldwide. Given our industrial relationship, the company can provide total solution from design to manufacturing with joint venture of our alliance companies.</profile></company><company><name>Lifewood Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 205A, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Lighthouse Technologies Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>lighthouse_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 531-537, 5/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2192-1688</tel><fax>(852) 2423-1092</fax><url>http://www.lighthouse-tech.com</url><email>info@lighthouse-tech.com</email><profile>Available through our extensive network of rental partners, Lighthouse LED screens are renown for their superior brightness and colors. They have quickly become the preferred option for indoor and outdoor applications worldwide. 

-	Form in January 1998 by leading industry experts

-	R&D facilities: Canada, Hong Kong & Southern China

-	Production: Southern China & Belgium

-	2000 Gold Peak Group with a market capitalization of $1,000m acquires 71% of Lighthouse

-	Global marketing and technical support: USA; Europe; Asia

Products  :
With one of the widest range of LED screens available, Lighthouse can meet any presentation, venue or advertising needs. Lighthouse LED video panels are self-contained and modular for simplicity of installation and operation. All Lighthouse products are built to ISO 9000 standard and are CE and FCC marked. The screen data is distributed using serial digital cabling and each panel has its own independent power supply. The processing unit will accept any video or PC input, whether it is analogue or digital.

Indoor Screens  :
The LVP05 5mm and the LVP10 10mm are the industry standard indoor screen and are used for a variety of applications.

Outdoor Screens  :
The LVP20 20mm and the LVP25 25mm are Lighthouse standard outdoor screens. They are used for a variety of applications.</profile></company><company><name>Linkz Industries Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 601-610, 6/F,, Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Sceince Park,, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>Ms. Serene Lo</person><tel>2410 3019</tel><fax>2422 2737</fax><url>www.http://Linkzinduries.com</url><email>serence@Linkzdustries.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>LumaTech Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit  112, 1/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Mark Wong</person><tel>(852) 2607-4075</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>http://www.luma-tech.com</url><email>mwong@luma-tech.com</email><profile>LumaTech is a fabless semiconductor company engaging in the development of Liquid Crystal Display (LCD) Controller Integrated Circuit (IC) devices. The image quality of its chip can be preserved when different resolution image converting from the computer to a fixed resolution LCD monitor. It is capable to support various LCD monitor panels in different resolutions through its software programmable options. Product applications include flat panel TV, PDA, mobile phones and portable DVD players.</profile></company><company><name>Luminant Technology Limited</name><industry>Telecom</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Stephen Yip</person><tel>(852) 2607-4188</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>http://www.luminantec.com</url><email>stephen@soundigit.com</email><profile>Luminant is developing a software that generates music as instrumental sounds for polyphonic application on mobile phones and other electrical or electronics appliances such as toys, timepiece, home appliances etc.</profile></company><company><name>M2 Laboratories Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 213, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Jean-Charles Andreani</person><tel>2607-4220</tel><fax>2607-4221</fax><url>/</url><email>info@m2-labs.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>MAS Technology Company Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 115, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>MIPS Technologies Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>mips.jpg</logo><location>Unit 217B, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T</location><person>Darwin So Wan Yun</person><tel>9773 3529</tel><fax>2607 4260</fax><url>http://www.mips.com.hk</url><email>darwinso@mips.com.hk</email><profile>The Company
Founded by a group of industrial professionals and engineering researchers, MIPS technologies is a solution provider focusing on the design, development and integration of advanced wireless and multimedia technologies. MIPS is specializing in MP3, MPEG4, JPEG, image processing, Bluetooth, GSM/GPRS, EDGE and especially location tracking technologies.


The Team
Our team has more than 7 years working experience in multinational companies and universities. We have a strong balance between theoretical and practical application experience. By making use of advanced wireless and signal processing technologies, rigorous software development process and version control system, we offer state-of-the-art wireless and multimedia embedded algorithms and applications. 


The service
MIPS is committed to providing high-quality and optimized DSP software, RF and baseband hardware tuned for our customer specific needs. We offer:
- novel GSM location tracking technologies and applications
- complete design service from system design, implementation and integration to various embedded platforms or products</profile></company><company><name>Macronix (Hong Kong) Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 702-703, 7/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607-4298</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4229</fax><url>http://www.mxic.com.tw</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Maunsell Consultants Asia Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 711-712, 7/F, BioInformatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6886</tel><fax>(852) 2629-1833</fax><url>http://www.maunsell.com.hk</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Memec (Asia Pacific) Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 705, 7/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2410-2728</tel><fax>(852) 2481-1496</fax><url>http://www.memec-asiapacific.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Microtech Innovation Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 710-713, 7/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Dick Cheung</person><tel>(852) 2178- 6888</tel><fax>(852) 2178- 6811</fax><url>http://www.microtechinno.com</url><email>dickcheung@microtechinno.com</email><profile>Solomon Microtech Limited is a Fabless IC design company.  Major products including smart card chips and smart card readers for both contact and contactless application.  The company also has very strong experience and capability in other microcontroller (MCU) design and development.</profile></company><company><name>MiniLogic Device Corporation Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 508-509, 5/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Stapler Li</person><tel>(852) 2319-1080</tel><fax>(852) 2776-9363</fax><url>http://www.minilogic.com.hk</url><email>sales@minilogic.com.hk</email><profile>Founded in Hong Kong in January 2000 with a worldwide sales network spanning Europe, China, Taiwan and Hong Kong, MiniLogic Device Corporation Ltd. is an IC design company committed to offering cost effective and fast turn-around solutions to customers. It specializes in developing static LCD drivers and module, power management IC and will be designing LCD information system at a later stage.</profile></company><company><name>Mosway Semiconductor Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 703, 7/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607-4123</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4060</fax><url>http://www.mosway.com</url><email>sales@mosway.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>National IC Design Industrial Base (Shenzhen) Institution - Hong Kong Representative Office</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 208B, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>National Semiconductor Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 110-121, 1/F, No.5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2655-6000</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4136</fax><url>http://www.nsc.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Net Caves Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/1162105675911/netcavelogo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 112, 1/F IC Development Centre, No. 6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Peter Kwok</person><tel>(852) 2686 9190</tel><fax>(852) 2686 9364</fax><url>www.netcaves.com / www.clinicideas.com</url><email>info@netcaves.com</email><profile>Net Caves is an IT solution provider focus on providing technical networking services and software design.

When it comes to distributing information technology products and services, it has committed itself to provide quality products and quality services. It has established itself as a high-tech provider comprised of team of professional engineers and programmers that set it apart from its competitors and made it choice for the Asia-pacific region's leading supplier of IT services and computer products.

Our vision is to help medical professionals to extend their productivity and service quality by making use of our cutting edge technologies. The business of general practices is changing every day. General practitioners have more work than they can cope with and they are struggling to meet the needs of their practice populations. They need tools that are easy to use, flexible, and with extensive reporting capabilities to offload the tedious work.</profile></company><company><name>Newbest Development Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>DirLogo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 311-312, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T</location><person>/</person><tel>2451 1628</tel><fax>2457 7000</fax><url>http://www.new-b.com</url><email>enquiry@new-b.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Noveon Asia Pacific Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 801-803 & 811-813, 8/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Christine Lam</person><tel>(852) 2508-1021</tel><fax>(852) 2503-1914</fax><url>http://www.noveoninc.com</url><email>christine.lam@noveoninc.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ON Semiconductor SCG Hong Kong SAR Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>on-semi.jpg</logo><location>Unit 201-215 & 235-238, 2/F, No.1 Science Park  East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2689-0088</tel><fax>(852) 2689-0080</fax><url>http://www.onsemi.com/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>ON Semiconductor (NASDAQ: ONNN) offers an extensive portfolio of power- and data-management semiconductors that address the design needs of today's sophisticated electronic products, appliances and automobiles. The company's technology portfolio is led by its power-management products that set the industry standard by reducing "leaky electricity" in everyday products and performs the precise management of power in today's sophisticated portable electronic devices.

The company has three main product lines: power management and standard analog integrated circuits (amplifiers, voltage references, interfaces and comparators); high-performance logic (application specific products, communication integrated circuits, clocks, translators and drivers); and standard semiconductors that include active discrete and MOSFET devices. ON Semiconductor leads the industry in the introduction of micro packages that offer increased performance characteristics while reducing the critical board space inside today's ever-shrinking electronic devices. The company's line of MicroIntegration and MicroLeadless products provide design engineers with increased flexibility to solve the most difficult design issues.</profile></company><company><name>Omron Electronic Components (Hong Kong) Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 218-220, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2768-1163</tel><fax>(852) 2375-0598</fax><url>http://www.omron.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Opto-electronic Display Devices Test & Measurement Laboratory</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>204B,Photonic Center, 2, Science Park Avenue East, Sha Tin , N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Optoelectronic Display Device Test & Measurement Laboratory</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 204B, 2/F, No.2 Science Park East Ave, Photonics Centre, Shatin, N.T</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>PCCW</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 308, 3/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629-6661</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>PMS Video Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 111-112, 1/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Nelson Choi</person><tel>(852) 2607-4055</tel><fax>(852) 3186-2352</fax><url>http://www.pmsvideo.com</url><email>nelson@pmsvideo.com</email><profile>PMS Video is a systems design company specializing in developing SDI (Serial Digital Interface) products, which allow consumers to enhance the image quality of digital output (e.g. Plasma TV, digital projector, LCD monitors) at lower cost.</profile></company><company><name>Paradigm Corporation Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 203, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2760 7811</tel><fax>(852) 2760 8738</fax><url>http://www.paradigm2000.com</url><email>mandymak@paradigm2000.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Perfisans Networks Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 206, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Hilbert Wong</person><tel>(852) 2144 2513</tel><fax>(852) 2144 2511</fax><url>http://www.perfisans.com</url><email>hwsavion@icare.com.hk</email><profile>Perfisans Networks is a fabless semi-conductor company which is planning to develop chips called System Network Accelerator (SNA). This chip will be implemented with the technology of TOE (TCP Offload Engine) to solve the problem on the network bottleneck which may be created when the CPU capacity cannot cope with the growing network speed. This technology helps ease the loading of the CPU by relocating the TCP/IP protocol from the CPU to the end product of the chip, which is a network interface card.</profile></company><company><name>Pericom Semiconductor (HK) Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>1pericom_logo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 326-332, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Joyce Hsu / Stephanie Mui</person><tel>(852) 2245-0100</tel><fax>(852) 2243-3998</fax><url>http://www.pericom.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>Pericom Semiconductor Corp., located in Silicon Valley, is a leading edge company that designs and markets high-performance logic and mixed signal integrated circuits for the computing, networking and data communication market. It is ranked as one of Forbes 200 Best Small Companies, listed on the NASDAQ stock exchange under "PSEM" and also added to the list of options that are traded on the Chicago Board Options Exchange. Effective from Oct 2, 2000, Pericom has been added to the Standard and Poors (S & P) Small Cap 600 Index.
The Hong Kong Technology Center is designing IC's for network servers, notebooks, routers and switches that enable internet bandwidth expansion.</profile></company><company><name>Philips Electronics HK Ltd (5/F)</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 501-520, 5/F, No. 5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 -2489 3025</tel><fax>852 - 2410 1648</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Philips Electronics HK Ltd (6/F)</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 601-620, 6/F, No. 5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>852 -2489 3025</tel><fax>852 - 2410 1648</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Philips Electronics Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 207-221, 2/F & whole floor 3/F - 6/F, No.5 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Steve Chan</person><tel>(852) 2489-6809</tel><fax>(852) 2418-6030</fax><url>http://www.philips.com</url><email>steve.chan_2@philips.com</email><profile>Philips Electronics of the Netherlands is one of the world’s biggest electronics companies and Europe’s largest, with sales of Euro 29 billion in 2003.  Philips Electronics Hong Kong plays a leading role within the group, globally.  Hong Kong is the regional operations hub for several of Philips’ businesses including Design, Lighting, Domestic Appliances & Personal Care and Medical Systems, and is also the global headquarters for Mobile Infotainment and Mobile Display Systems.  The Park’s campus environment is well suited for Philips to generate synergistic forces.  Operating under one roof with its product planning teams, research & development centre, design studio and head office functions will boost the company’s efficiency and innovation competence in the territory and the Asia Pacific Region.</profile></company><company><name>Pixel Magic Systems Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>1pericom_logo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 603 & 605, 6/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Nelson Choi</person><tel>(852) 2607-4055</tel><fax>(852) 3186-2352</fax><url>http://www.pixelmagicsystems.com</url><email>nelson@pixelmagicsystems.com</email><profile>Pixel Magic Systems Ltd., the leading home theater video processing manufacturer and developer, is bringing broadcast video picture quality to home theater consumers by its Serial Digital Interface (SDI) products including its own brand Crystalio video processors/scalers.
It developed and manufactured the first Linux-based video processor (Crystalio® VPS-2300) for home theater market in the world.  Crystalio® VPS-2300 offers users the freedom to convert both high definition (e.g.1080i) and standard definition video input to a customized progressive resolution which can be perfectly matched to the native resolution of the digital display (including 1080p) and output digitally to a DVI compatible display. Technologies including DCDiTM and TrueLife® are employed to provide impressive de-interlaced processing and outstanding picture quality. 
Through its distribution networks, Pixel Magic Systems products are now being sold in more than 15 countries worldwide.</profile></company><company><name>Probe and Test Development Centre</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G01A, G/F Innovation Centre, 6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok, N.T.</location><person>.</person><tel>852-2629 6600</tel><fax>852-2629 6600</fax><url>.</url><email>helpdesk@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>.</profile></company><company><name>QRG Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210A, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>REnex Technology Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/1048132768298/renex_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 601-603, 6/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2607-4088</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.raesystems.com</url><email>raesales@raesystems.com</email><profile>REnex Technology Ltd which was incorporated in Hong Kong in may 2000, is 40% owned by the Hong Kong based RAE Systems Asia Ltd which is a wholly-owned subsidiary of RAE Systems Inc in USA.

RAE Systems Inc. was established in 1991 by co-founders Robert I. Chen and Peter Hsi. Today, RAE Systems is recognized as one of the World's leading manufacturers of technologically advanced single and multiple sensor atmospheric monitors, photo-ionization detectors, gas detection tubes, sampling pumps, and wirelessly connected gas detection and security monitoring systems.

Based in the heart of "Silicon Valley", RAE Systems is a progressive, high-tech company with manufacturing and distribution networks spanning the entire globe. In 1999 RAE Systems moved into its new World Headquarters facility in Sunnyvale, California. The high-tech headquarters facility offers over 2,300 square meters of research and manufacturing space. RAE Systems' fully owned offshore operations provide over 2,000 square meters of additional manufacturing space. In 2001 RAE Systems broke ground on a new facility in Shanghai, China, that will offer an additional 20,000 square meters of state-of-the-art manufacturing and product development space. RAE Systems is truly positioned for global future growth.

Products  :

RAE Systems products are used to detect and measure a wide variety of dangerous atmospheric contaminants and conditions such as combustible gas and vapor accumulations, oxygen deficiencies, and toxic gases such as carbon monoxide, hydrogen sulfide, carbon dioxide, and many other commonly encountered atmospheric hazards. RAE Systems' patented photo-ionization detector technology allows dependable, linear, part-per-million range readings for many toxic gases and vapors that are effectively undetectable by any other means. The Company's products are particularly well suited for the measurement of volatile organic compounds such as gasoline, benzene, paints, degreasers, jet fuel, and most organic solvents. The Company's proprietary, patent protected technology has made it the World's Leading Manufacturer of portable photo-ionization detector equipped instruments. The Company's products are used in weapons of mass destruction (WMD), environmental, safety, HAZMAT, toxic industrial chemical (TIC), petrochemical, semiconductor, and confined space entry monitoring programs all over the world.

RAE Systems' monitors are used in civilian and government atmospheric monitoring programs in over 50 countries. The Company's products are used in all major United States manufacturing industries, as well by numerous city, state and federal agencies and departments. A substantial number of municipal agencies and city departments have standardized their programs on RAE Systems' products for confined space and HAZMAT incident response. RAE Systems is also the leading supplier of gas detectors used for jet fuel vapor monitoring programs. Commercial aviation customers with sizable numbers of RAE Systems' instruments include American Airlines, United Airlines and US Airways. RAE Systems' customers include many of the World's Leading corporations, such as General Motors, Honda, Exxon, IBM, Mobil, Dow, Texaco, DuPont, Chevron, Hewlett-Packard, British Petroleum, Amoco, Motorola, Boeing and Intel.

RAE Systems has significant numbers of instruments currently in service with the United States Navy, Marine Corps, Army, Air Force, Canadian Department of Defense, Environmental Protection Agency, Occupational Safety and Health Administration, and the Department of Justice (including the FBI, Treasury Department, Secret Service, and Drug Enforcement Agency). RAE Systems instruments are used in a wide variety of programs for the detection of vapors associated with explosives, nerve agents, CWAs, TICs, and as part of the personal protective equipment issued to bomb-disposal, hostage-rescue, clandestine crime lab, hazardous material (HAZMAT), and other high-risk response teams throughout the country. To date, RAE Systems has over 3,000 instruments fielded with these various United States government departments, agencies and programs.

RAE Systems' commitment to quality can be seen in every aspect of the Company's business. The Company's Quality Systems constantly reinforce our customer focused culture of continues improvement. In 1998 RAE Systems completed registration of the Company's Quality Systems to ISO 9001. In 1999 we completed registration of our international manufacturing subsidiary in Shanghai, China, to ISO 9002. In 2001 RAE Systems achieved European Community (ATEX) Certification for the Company's Product Quality Systems.

-	Wireless networked
-	PID
-	Confined space
-	Single gas monitors
-	Multi-gas monitors
-	IAQ
-	Fixed systems
-	Tubes & pumps</profile></company><company><name>RHT Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 107, 1/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Radica Systems Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 102 & 116, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2866-1106</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4211</fax><url>http://www.radicasys.com</url><email>info@radicasys.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Radioscape Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 333, 3/F,, No.1 Science Park West Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Phil Smith</person><tel>(852) 3471 0200</tel><fax>(852) 2367 2090</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Red Jasper Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 210, 2/F, Building 9, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>Mr. Andrew Lim</person><tel>6423 3389</tel><fax>2358 4931</fax><url>http://www.redjasper.com</url><email>info@redjasper.com</email><profile>Red Jasper’s mission is to harness advanced research in logistics and supply chain from the academia to create innovative products and applications that generate value to our clients. We aspire towards building unparalleled alliances and long term relationships with companies of complementary strengths so that extraordinary value can be extricated and realized.

It is a widely held view that research is light years ahead of industrial applications. We contend, in our relentless effort to distinguish ourselves and our clients, that designing cutting edge products and applications requires the necessity to first adapt the best research results and assimilate it to fully address the needs of each individual client. 

Being consistently at the forefront of research and development, Red Jasper is poised to emerge a champion from the competition pack. We are able to leverage on a unique blend of superior technological expertise and a formidable management team to craft effective, efficient and innovative systems using only the latest, most appropriate technologies and standards. We have successfully integrated these new and totally applicable systems into the current workflows for our clients. 

To the markets that Red Jasper serves, we are steadfast and focused on delivering real value and exceeding every expectation, always bearing in mind that our ultimate corporate objective is to empower our clients with tomorrow’s technologies today.</profile></company><company><name>RedRock Semiconductor Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 105-106, 1/F, Innovation Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Al Kwok</person><tel>(852) 2668-4537</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4069</fax><url>http://www.redrocksemi.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>Based on the technology in previous IC (named as RS-1), RedRock will develop a second IC (named as RS-2) which can provide a low cost, low power multimedia IC solution to mobile phone and PDA manufactures, enabling them to provide multimedia and gaming application in their wireless applications. RS-1 and RS-2 can process various kind of media content, such as MP3 playback, multimedia messaging (MMS), video on demand (VOD), location based services and games.</profile></company><company><name>Rodsum Wireless Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 108, 1/F,, IC Development Centre,, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok,, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Rogers Southeast Asia Inc.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 217, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Colin Kwan</person><tel>8236 6060</tel><fax>8236 6123</fax><url>/</url><email>colin.kwan@rogerscor</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SAE Magnetics (HK) Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>G/F - 6/F, SAE Technology Centre, No.6 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Horris Leung</person><tel>(852) 2612-8319</tel><fax>(852) 2480-4757</fax><url>http://hr.sae.com.hk/</url><email>horris@sae.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SEM RF Technologies Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>SEMLogo1.jpg</logo><location>Unit 222A-B, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Philip Pang</person><tel>2851 7833</tel><fax>2815 3929</fax><url>/</url><email>ppang@semrf.com</email><profile>SEM RF Technologies Limited (SRF) was founded in response to the Hong Kong Government’s objective to develop Hong Kong into a leading digital city in globally connected world of the 21st century.  Its initiative is also to leverage Hong Kong’s strengths in developing and establishing Hong Kong as a center of RF technologies in the next generation of wireless communications field.

SRF’S ultimate business objective is to develop the most advanced and state-of-art Multi-Function Modules (MFM) in the world.  SRF has already had eleven designs of Single Function Module (SFM) Power Amplifier (PA) that outperform other similar products in the market.  The two-stage SFM PAs, used in various 802.11a/b/g Wireless Local Area Network (WLAN) systems and Handset applications are available and ready for customer evaluation.  The design for three-stage SFM PAs for 802.11a/b/g WLAN card bus and access point application are also completed while designs for MFM PA are progressing in the roadmap.

SRF’S research and development involves a combination of mixed technologies with embedded passives and packaging for the interconnection, filtering and size reduction for our customers who demand for lower costs, smaller size, repeatable performance, improved quality manufacturing and few part counts.</profile></company><company><name>Scarborough</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 318-325, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2413-2890</tel><fax>(852) 2411-2360</fax><url>/</url><email>marketing@scarbo.com</email><profile>Founded in HK, Scarborough was a privately held company with less than 20 employees and a 3,000 sq. ft. factory. Nowadays, Scarborough has matured to a corporation with more than 800 staff and 128,000 sq. ft. facilities. From its inception in 1995, Scarborough (H.K.) Limited has committed itself to become a premier designer and manufacturer of high precision equipment and tooling. In few short years, the company has evolved into a well-recognized player in the industry and act as an international turnkey manufacturing solutions supplier. Products : Total solution provider on High Precision Engineering Service, including Build to Print Parts Machining, OEM & Contract Manufacturing Service, Quality Design on Production Jig & Fixture, Tailor-made Automation Equipment and Precision Mould & Die. Services : One-Stop Shopping, Engineering, Machining, Contract Manufacturing, Preventive Maintenance, and Program Management.</profile></company><company><name>Sengital Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 207, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Alan Lam</person><tel>(852) 2144-2628</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2623</fax><url>http://www.sengital.com</url><email>alan@sengital.com</email><profile>Virtual Reality Motion Sensing (VRMS) is an all-encompassing technology that involves the integration of low-cost MEMS motion sensors, wireless transmitters, low-power circuit design and proprietary software to create small footprint, low-power consumption motion sensing systems. 

Based on this technology, our immediate focus is to bring several products to market within 1.5 years. These can be classified into 3 categories: 1) computer input devices and multi-functional game controllers, 2) mobile platform interface devices, and 3) sports, exercise, ergonomics, and human rehabilitation (gait measurement) module. 

VRMS technology, enables the design of sourceless, head, hand, and body tracking devices useful for 3-D or 'Space' mice, advanced head tracking systems for head mounted displays, three and six degree of freedom devices, and new input devices yet to be conceived.</profile></company><company><name>Service Apartment</name><industry>Facility Management</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 501-519, 5/F, No.1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2639-8248</tel><fax>(852) 2655-8668</fax><url>http://www.hksciencepark.org</url><email>frontdesk@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ShaoLin Microsystems Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 220, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. David Chow</person><tel>(852) 2352-5568</tel><fax>(852) 2352-5576</fax><url>http://www.shaolinmicro.com</url><email>davidchow@shaolinmicro.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Shinki Corporation of Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 318, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2149-6652</tel><fax>(852) 2149-6659</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SiTel Semiconductor HK Ltd</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 223, 2/F, No. 1 Science Park West Ave, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. H.K. Teoh</person><tel>2737 1708</tel><fax>2314 9424</fax><url>http://www.sitelsemi.com</url><email>hk.teoh@sitelsemi.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SigmaTel Asia Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 601-603, 6/F Building 1, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, NT</location><person>Mr. Jose Lau</person><tel>2627 5088</tel><fax>2175 5050</fax><url>http://www.sigmatel.com</url><email>jlau@sigmatel.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Silver Coral Limited (Promo Group TV)</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 701 & 720, 7/F,, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Pak Shek Kok, Sha Tin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Ko Ping Yeung</person><tel>2824 8662</tel><fax>2824 8291</fax><url>http://www.promogroup.tv</url><email>pyko@promogroup.tv</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SinoMab BioScience Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 508, 5/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Simon Kwong</person><tel>2152 0388</tel><fax>2152 0222</fax><url>http://www.sinomab.com</url><email>simon@sinomab.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Skyworks Solution Worldwide, Inc.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 218-219, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2655-8755</tel><fax>(852) 2598-8722</fax><url>http://www.skyworksinc.com</url><email>hilda.kwong@skyworksinc.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Socom Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 202B, 2/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Simon Tang</person><tel>(852) 2607 4139</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4198</fax><url>http://www.socom.com.hk</url><email>simon@socom.com.hk</email><profile>SOCOM LIMITED uses revolutionary, cutting edge, proprietary technology in developing and manufacturing (internal and/or outsource) high-quality 2G, 2.5G and 3G wireless telecommunication base station infrastructure products that provide superior performance at low cost for sales to network suppliers and service providers. 

Technologies 
Radio interference and noise are the key determinant of network capacity and coverage in wireless networks. For the designer, there are always trade-off between performance, size, and cost. Traditional band-pass filtering and antennas lack directional selectivity, which makes noise and interference problems worse. SOCOM LIMITED on has developed breakthrough proprietary technology that it will apply and deliver in its key wireless infrastructure products to provide superior performance at low cost. Our solutions also reduce co-channel interference, increase range and capacity. 

Main Products 
1) Uplink at Tower Top System (UATTS). Improves sensitivity and selectivity of wireless receivers, increase uplink services coverage and improves signal quality at low cost. 
2) Narrow Beam Antenna System (NBAS). Expands service coverage and improves signal quality for both uplink and downlink wireless communication transmissions at low cost. NBAS distribution and control system is entirely different from conventional Smart Antenna (SA). 
3) Wireless Transmitter Power Amplifier (WTPA). Uses proprietary, patented components, subsystem, and digital technology. Solves downlink capability problem and saves operating cost. Improves transmission signal quality with double the over all efficiency of transmitter.</profile></company><company><name>SofTech Microsystems Asia Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 322, 3/F, Building 2,, No.1 Science Park West Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>Mr. Roy Yeung</person><tel>3543 0500</tel><fax>3543 0505</fax><url>www.http://softecmicro.com</url><email>honoho yeung@softecmicro.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Solomon Systech Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>SolomonSystech_vert-logo_jpg-1.jpg</logo><location>3/F - 6/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Yvonne Chan</person><tel>(852) 2207-1111</tel><fax>(852) 2267-0800</fax><url>http://www.solomon-systech.com</url><email>sales@solomon-systech.com</email><profile>Founded in 1999, Solomon Systech Limited is a leading flat panel display IC company for high-tech products, providing display IC solutions on an international basis under its own global brand.  With a “fabless” business model, the Group specializes in the design, development and sales of proprietary IC solutions that enable a wide range of display applications for cellular phones, computer monitors, flat panel TVs and PDAs etc.

Solomon Systech (International) Limited’s shares are listed on Main Board of the Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited on 8 April 2004 with a stock code: 2878. . It is also one of the constituent stocks on the Hang Seng HK SmallCap Index under the Hang Seng Composite Index. 

More information about the Group, its products and services may be obtained at: http://www.solomon-systech.com.</profile></company><company><name>South Sea Semiconductor Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 505, 5/F, IC Development Centre, Building 5, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, NT</location><person>Dr. Sze-Hon Kwan</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.southseasemi.com</url><email>lesliekwan@southseasemi.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SpeedNet Communication International Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>speednetlogo.jpg</logo><location>Unit 207, 2/F Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Kan Ma</person><tel>(852) 2455 1565</tel><fax>(852) 8113 0417</fax><url>http://www.speednet.com.hk</url><email>enq@speednet.com.hk</email><profile>SpeedNet Communication International Ltd. is an electronic engineering company base in Hong Kong engaged in automobile aftermarket, specializing in researching, developing, producing and marketing of Safety Early Warning Diagnostic System for Drivers. 
SpeedNet with one goal in mind: to make an affordable, yet sophisticated, personal Safety Early Warning Diagnostic System for Drivers. It provides multi-functions including diagnostic solutions for most of your OBDII compliant vehicles, monitor real-time data such as Speed, RPM, coolant temperature,  oxygen sensor values etc…, reset the Check Engine Light (MIL) and what's more... we endeavor to make you always drive in safety by providing you to set warning point alert according to your specific need. 

SpeedNet is committed to producing high-end personal diagnostics solutions and providing world-class support to its customers.</profile></company><company><name>Speedpixel Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 106, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Michael Chan</person><tel>(852) 9640-2517</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.speed-pixel.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>Speedpixel is founded with the target to improve the end user experience of video and audio monitor system using a digital approach.</profile></company><company><name>Starlims Asia Pacific Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 701-702, No. 2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Linus Chu</person><tel>2793 0699</tel><fax>2793 0116</fax><url>http://www.starlims.com</url><email>linus@starlims.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Sun Microsystems IC Training Centre</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 308D, 3/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2629- 6635</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Sunpet Industries Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit G09, No. 5 Science Park West Ave.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Supply Chain & Logistics Technology Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 223-226, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2997-7799</tel><fax>(852) 2997-7711</fax><url>http://www.sclnet.com.hk</url><email>info@sclnet.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>SwiftPath (HK) Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 213, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Jack Poon</person><tel>(852) 2144-2100</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2166</fax><url>http://www.swiftpath.com</url><email>jack_poon@swiftpath.com</email><profile>The company plans to develop software which is a proprietary mobile data transmission protocol called DAVIP (Data Audio Visual Intelligent Protocol) which enables the transmission of data and multimedia signal be done in a mode of “thin-client”. The product can be sold as a software or it can be embedded into IC. Although the end products are proprietary, the targeted market is mainly consumer and it can be applied to wireless applications such as mobile phones, PDAs, or for SOHO users.</profile></company><company><name>Synapse Microelectronics Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Tong Man Ki, Simon</person><tel>2380 3816</tel><fax>2380 3816</fax><url>http://www.whatissynapse.com</url><email>simon@whatissynapse.com</email><profile>Synapse Microelectronics Limited is an R&D company focusing on the development of automatic inspection machines.  Our first machine solution delivered is the Automatic Optical Inspection (AOI) Machine that is used for error checking of Printed Circuit Board (PCB) Layouts.

PCB layout cannot be guaranteed 100% accurate in fabrication.  Layout must be inspected and re-worked to correct the errors before processing steps that are irreversible.  Traditionally, this job is done by human eye inspection.  Speed is slow and reliability is limited.  The issue is worsened with the advance of technology towards narrower trace width.

Purpose of the AOI machine is to automate the work of PCB layout checking, accuracy verifying, possible defects locating and displaying for user re-work.

By doing a specialized design on our electronic circuitry and having a detailed research on our error checking algorithm, our AOI machine achieved advantages of a reduced number of false alarm, fast processing speed, improved location accuracy and low power consumption.

Using our new AOI system, yield rate and production speed of PCB manufacturing can be highly improved.  Quality of PCB shipped will also be guaranteed.  As a result, the manufacturing cost will be reduced substantially.</profile></company><company><name>Synopsys(HKSP)Customer Support Office</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>308C, Innovation Center, 6, Science Park West Avenue, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>TPO Displays Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 311-322, 3/F,, No. 5 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>www.tpo.biz</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Tec-Hill</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 538-543, 5/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2370-8818</tel><fax>(852) 2370-8829</fax><url>http://www.tec-hill.com</url><email>enquiry@tec-hill.com</email><profile>Founded since March, 1991 Tec-Hill Company Limited has evolved speedily to a leading manufacturer of memory modules and CompactFlash cards, and also a well-known distributor of SDRAM, DRAM, SRAM, Flash Memory, CPU, Hard Disk Drive, Microcontroller, and other computer components in the international market.

Tec-Hill's memory products include 168-pin and 144-pin DIMMs for PC133/100/66, and 72 pins SIMMs for upgrading on PC, workstation, server and notebook. Memory capacity ranges from 8MB to 512MB for different applications and needs. With the most advanced assembling under strict quality control and compatibility test for different applications. Besides, lifetime warranty and replacement on defective items are provided.</profile></company><company><name>Techful Electronics Industrial Co. Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 221, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin N.T.</location><person>Mr. Peter Ho</person><tel>(852) 3428-5535</tel><fax>(852) 3428-5997</fax><url>http://www.techful.net</url><email>peterho@techful.net</email><profile>達科電子實業有限公司是一間專門設計電子產品服務的科技顧問公司。達科提供的電子產品設計及應用開發服務，不單可以用於純電子產品，更可以應用在不同的領域，配合各行各業發展及需要。我們細心聆聽每一位客戶的需要，以待客至誠的精神，豐富的經驗及完善的技術支援系統，為客戶提供度身訂造的電子設計以及生產，協助客戶達至最高的成本效益，務求使產品能夠在市場上佔一席位。
本公司貫徹嚴謹及專業的服務態度，為不同的客戶提供最優質的服務，務求使製作做到創新，專業，認真，嚴謹。</profile></company><company><name>Techno (Hong Kong) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 506, 5/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, NT</location><person>Mr. Lap Chow</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>chow@intetronics.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>The Hong Kong Association For Computer Education</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 116G, 1/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Think Technology International Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 308, 3/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Thomson Asia Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 315-316, 3/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Jasy Chan</person><tel>2686 0325</tel><fax>2686 2450</fax><url>http://www.thomson.net</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Thomson Hong Kong Holdings Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit (311-313) 3/F & 5/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>K.M .Lo</person><tel>(852) 2686-2222</tel><fax>(852) 2686-2290</fax><url>http://www.thomson.net</url><email>kam-moon.lo@thomson.net</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Timeless Software Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 111-113, 1/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin</location><person>Mr. Louis Fung</person><tel>2514 9211</tel><fax>2519 6010</fax><url>http://www.timeless.com.hk</url><email>louis.fung@timeless.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Traxon Technologies Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 208-213, 2/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Tri-Star Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 208 A&B, Building 9, No.5 Science Park West Avenue,, HKSP, Shatin, NT</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Twinberries Technologies Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 212, 2/F, IC Development Centre,, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Richard Chan</person><tel>(852) 3576 3031</tel><fax>(852) 2340 7561</fax><url>http://www.twinberries.com</url><email>richard@twinberries.com</email><profile>P&A承诺为客户提供优质可靠的服务；我们更以合理的价格，殷勤的售后服务，确保每位顾客都感到满意。
Label Technology And Automation Limited (P&A) is an engineering solution provider to help our clients develop robust solutions in label automation such as mechatronic labeling system, label software and RFID middleware fully compliant with EPCglobal standard. 

P&A is sophisticated at developing a series of products suit for use in the packaging business. This accelerates process flow automation in any fast expanding manufacturing industry such as pharmacy, chain stores and facilitates efficiency-demanded supply chain environment, using enabled and the latest technologies.

As a professional engineering service provider, we are fully committed to delivering high quality and practical product solutions. In achieving our commitment, we are adopting leading CAD models in product design, digital simulation and optimization, as well as process flow scenario analysis. This can also accelerate close cooperation among users, designers and fabricators. To help visualize the enhanced supply chain workflow before full investment is made, we provide our clients with digital animation in 3D environment.

    Our performance pledge is to provide our clients with the top quality products, high reliability and the best after-sale service, at a competitive price.</profile></company><company><name>Uniforce System Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 319, 3/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Francis Kam</person><tel>(852) 2446-4316</tel><fax>(852) 2191-8185</fax><url>http://www.uniforce.net</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>United Luminous International (Holding) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 611-620, 6/F,, Photonics Centre, No. 2 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park,, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>Ms. Serene Lo</person><tel>2410 3019</tel><fax>2422 2737</fax><url>www.http://Linkzindustries.com</url><email>serene@Linkzindustries.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Universal Technologies Holdings Ltd.</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 231-233, 2/F, No.1 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Tang Fei Piu</person><tel>(852) 2647-4230</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4288</fax><url>http://www.uth.com.hk</url><email>fptang@uth.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>University & Professional Association Representative Offices</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 116, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>V.ABC Group Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 213, 2/F, Bio-Informatics Centre,, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2947 7335</tel><fax>(852) 2690 9570</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>VP Dynamics Labs (LCD-TV) Limited</name><industry>Precision Engineering</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 202, 2/F, Photonics Centre, No.2 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Dr. Felix Lor, Visual Perception Manager</person><tel>(852) 2607-4228</tel><fax>(852) 8147-9887</fax><url>http://www.vp-dynamics.com</url><email>felixlor@vp-dynamics.com</email><profile>The company has developed and patented a low cost display resolution enhancement method for CSTN, TFT-LCD, OLED, PDP... displays using Visual Perception (VP) Technology 視感科技 and by applying such technology in the driver chipset in combination with a special subpixel arranged display panel, the resolution can be largely enhanced without increasing the number of pixels, thus it can provide enormous saving in manufacturing costs.
In TV applications, VP Technology enhances the video quality while minimizing the saw-tooth artefacts in moving pictures resulted from the de-interlacing process.  
In mobile applications, VP displays in QVGA and VGA resolution can be respectively incorporated into a tiny display of 1.6" and 2.0” diagonal for unmatched picture and video quality in 2.5G – 3G mobile phone display applications in MMS, Camera and TV mode. 
VP technology finds its place also in digital camera, PDA, projector, near-to-eye microdisplay and personal TV displays in airplanes, trains, boats, cars and home. 

Our vision is to make the display world more enjoyable and affordable.</profile></company><company><name>Vascular and Interventional Radiology Foundation</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 108, 1/F, Building 6, Bio-Informatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T</location><person>Dr. Simon C.H. Yu</person><tel>2632 2285</tel><fax>2648 4122</fax><url>/</url><email>simonyu@cuhk.edu.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Vcast (Asia) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 109-110, 1/F.,, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Keith Lie</person><tel>2121 8899</tel><fax>2121 8898</fax><url>http://www.vcast.net</url><email>keith@vcast.net</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ViDeOnline Communications (Asia) Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201-203, 2/F,, No. 5 Science Park East Avenue,, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N. T.</location><person>Ms. Amy Tsang</person><tel>2354 8138</tel><fax>2776 5235</fax><url>www.http://videonline.com</url><email>atsang@videonline.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ViMax Interactive Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 206, 2/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>ViXS Systems HK Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 601, 6/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park  West  Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Donna Wong</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>dwong@vixs.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Virtus Asia, Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/1170503693921/VA.jpg</logo><location>Unit 113, 1/F IC Development Centre, No. 6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Cherry Cheung</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>cherry.cheung@virtusensors.com</email><profile>Virtus Asia, Limited is focused on conducting R&D and will develop new end-user products utilizing its motion sensing technology which includes multi-axis accelerometers and gyros based on MEMS (Micro Electro Mechanical Systems) technology.    Virtus Asia works closely with local university research institutes, including the Chinese University of Hong Kong's (CUHK) Centre for Micro and Nano Systems.  
 
Virtus Asia Ltd. is an affiliated company of US-based Virtus Advanced Sensors (VAS).  VAS also maintains a wholly-owned subsidiary in Japan, Virtus Japan K.K., based in Tokyo.</profile></company><company><name>Vizibis Solutions Co.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 216B, 2/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Voiceware Electronics Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 113 & 115, 1/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Raymond Wong</person><tel>(852) 2144-2528</tel><fax>(852) 2144-2529</fax><url>http://www.vehk.com</url><email>raywong@vehk.com</email><profile>Voiceware develops proprietary compression and decompression algorithms for voice processing by means of a low cost DSP (Digital Signal Processor) integrated circuit at low compression rate enabling quality playback sound. The DSP chip can be applied on language learning aid devices, digital recording devices and the broadcasting language learning lesson programs via Internet and electronic dictionary.</profile></company><company><name>Vtech Corporate Services Ltd</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 606-607, 6/F,, IC development Centre, No. 6 Science Park West Ave, Science Park, Shatin, NT</location><person>Mr. Chang Yu Wai</person><tel>2680 5041</tel><fax>2665 5099</fax><url>http://www.vtech.com</url><email>vw_chang@vtech.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>WE3 Technology Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 108-113, 1/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.we3technology.com</url><email>info@we3technology.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Wavecom Asia Pacific Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 201-207 &215, 2/F, Bio-Informatics Centre, No.2 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Pak Shek Kok, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Dider Dutronc</person><tel>2824-5255</tel><fax>2824-5488</fax><url>http://www.wavecom.com.hk</url><email>didier.dutronc@wavecom.com.hk</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>We Software Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>wesoft_ds.jpg</logo><location>Unit 335-337, 3/F, No.1 Science Park East  Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 3188-2929</tel><fax>(852) 3188-2939</fax><url>http://www.wesoft.com</url><email>enquiry@wesoft.com</email><profile>WeSoft is a leading embedded software engineering company in Asia, focusing on embedded software solutions targeting Internet Appliances (IA) manufacturers and technology vendors in the US, Europe and Asian markets.
Founded in 1997 with headquarters located in Hong Kong, this technology intensive company has developed its expertise through corporations with company in US and Asian area.
The company was found originally to do outsourcing software testing, quality assurance and development for US software firms.

Our product line includes WebEverywhereTM (an Embedded Web browser), iProtocol Suite (an Embedded TCP/IP stacks software), NetPassportTM and AirPassportTM (Security solution for E-Commerce transactions based on PKI standard). In addition, We Soft offers a complete set of engineering consulting services to satisfy specific needs of different customers.</profile></company><company><name>Westline Security Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 207B, 2/F, Building 9, No. 5 Science Park West Ave, Hong Kong Science Park</location><person>Mr. Albert Hui</person><tel>(852) 2824 8911</tel><fax>(852) 2824 8365</fax><url>/</url><email>ahui@westline.net</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>WideFly Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 202B, 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Win Key Information Technology Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 211, 2/F, No. 5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>2607 4231</tel><fax>2607 4130</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Winfield International Agricultural Science Eco Management and Development Co., Ltd.</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 304, 3/F, No. 1 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Charles Suen</person><tel>2868 1236</tel><fax>2905 1566</fax><url>/</url><email>unitak2i@netvigator.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Xilinx Hong Kong Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 101-107, 1/F, Wireless Centre, No.3 Science Park East Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Ms. Petulia Wong</person><tel>(852) 2401 5106</tel><fax>(852) 3107 0074</fax><url>http://www.xilinx.com</url><email>pet.wong@xilinx.com</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>Zensis Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>1185269081609_1zensis-7.jpg</logo><location>Unit 203, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin N.T.</location><person>Picco Chu</person><tel>(852) 2607-4113</tel><fax>(852) 2607-4260</fax><url>http://www.zensis.com</url><email>picco@zensis.com</email><profile>Zensis develops state-of-art technologies focusing in digital imaging and mobile applications for the global corporate and consumer market. Founded in 2003, the core technologies of Zensis, PhotoRite and VideoRite, are US patent-pending technologies that automatically correct common problems and significantly improve the visual quality of photos and videos. 

Based on these technologies, Zensis has developed multimedia applications and software modules that allow users and device manufacturers to enhance, enrich and edit photos and videos in a very easy way. They run not only on PC, but also on mobile phones, digital still camera and other handheld devices, as firmware, software module, and software products.

Zensis has released several popular software products for home users, all of them have the powerful “1-Click Autofix” function; they are:

PhotoRite FX – The PC software that let computer beginners edit photos professionally. The user friendly UI and powerful features make it the best PC photo editing software to edit photos efficiently and easily. User can use Batch Mode to AutoFix, resize and rename a batch of photos with just a few mouse clicks.

PhotoRite SP – The mobile software that let users take quality enhanced photos anytime, anywhere. It features other functions such as Extendable Photo Frames, Slim Up, Magic Mirror filters, Soft Lens, etc. The Symbian Series 60 version is currently the best-selling Symbian imaging app in the market.</profile></company><company><name>atest2</name><industry>Incubation</industry><logo>1186110795078_phi1.2.jpg</logo><location>/</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>findsomeone@somewhere.com</email><profile>en
測試中2长度2findsomeone@somewhere.com
<>!@#$%^&*()\/</profile></company><company><name>e-jing Technologies Limited</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 101, 1/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>(852) 2851-2321</tel><fax>(852) 2994-2078</fax><url>http://www.e-jing.net</url><email>enquiry@e-jing.net</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>eNext Microdevices Incorporation Limited</name><industry>Semiconductor</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 203A 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>Mr. Kenneth Wong</person><tel>(852) 2607 4278</tel><fax>(852) 2607 4279</fax><url>/</url><email>kenneth.wong@enextmicro.com</email><profile>New startup company focused on next generation EMI and ESD technologies by integration of discrete into silicon and address mass volume applications in mobile, digital multimedia and computer.
  A solid executive team with strong experience in semiconductor, mobile and consumer electronics
  Expertise in analog chip design, chip processing and packaging technologies</profile></company><company><name>eNext Microdevices Incorporation Limited</name><industry>Not Specified</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 203A 2/F, IC Development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>iNah Multimedia Company Limited</name><industry>Electronics/Video/HDTV</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 220, 2/F, No.5 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin N.T.</location><person>Mr. Kenneth Yeung</person><tel>(852) 2557 7755</tel><fax>(852) 2551-9779</fax><url>http://www.inahgroup.com</url><email>ykyeung@inahgroup.com</email><profile>iNah is a system design company which develops consumer digital electronics products. The products which are planned to develop include Portable Multimedia Player (PMP) and wireless video phone. The company will use Philips media processor (Nexperta PNX 1500) as a core which supports video, audio, graphics and communications data-streaming. The PMP has a built-in 20G hard disk and a 4" color TFT LCD, as eell as TV and FM turners. The wireless video phone is in fact a FRS (Family Radio Service) walkie-talkie incorporated with a TFT LCD and a CMOS image senor to allow video and audio communication within a range of few miles. It will develop other kind of products such as Internet set top box and digital video camera at a in later stage utilizing the same media processor.</profile></company><company><name>nVidia Singapore Pte. Ltd.</name><industry>Information Technology</industry><logo>/</logo><location>Unit 501-503, 5/F, IC development Centre, No.6 Science Park West Avenue, Hong Kong Science Park, Shatin, N.T.</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>http://www.nvidia.com</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company><company><name>tpo display hk limited</name><industry>Electronics</industry><logo>/</logo><location>hksp</location><person>/</person><tel>/</tel><fax>/</fax><url>/</url><email>admin@hksciencepark.org</email><profile>/</profile></company></tenant>